（古市）魔界に帰る？誰が？
Going back to the Demon World?
（男鹿）医者だよ　医者。
Who?
The doctor guy.
あのちっこいのと　テキトーな奴。
The squirt and the one with
half-assed character design.
（ゲーム）敵が現れた！
An enemy has appeared!
ベル坊が回復して
も～やる事もね～からな…。
With Baby Beel all better, they
didn't have any reason to be here.
そろそろ魔界に帰るんだとよ。
They said it was about time they
headed back to the Demon World.
（古市）ふ～ん　ほんまかい。
うっ…。
Seriously...
HonMAKAI
Honmakai = Seriously
Makai = Demon World
えっ！？
（ベル坊）えっ！？
Are you Kidding Me? The Demon World
（ラミア）さむっ…→
HonMAKAI
Lame!
な～に　今のギャグ
もう一回　言ってみてよ。
Just try saying that pun again.
あたしたち　魔界へ帰るんだ～
ほれ。
We're heading back to the Demon World!
Come on...
うるせ～よ！とっとと帰れ！
Shut up! Just go already!
（ラフマニノフ）
うむ　そのつもりなのだが
アランドロンがつかまらんのだ。→
That was our intent.
But I can't seem to find Alaindelon.
君　一緒に住んでいるのだろう
何か知らないか？
You live together with him,
yes? Do you know anything?
いや　知らないッスけど。
そうか…困ったの。
Nope, I dunno.
I see. That is a problem.
師匠　やっぱり今日は
やめにしましょうよ。
Doctor, why don't we wait until tomorrow?
ベルゼ様と　もう少しいたいし。
I wanna stay together with
Beelze-sama a little longer!
（ラフマニノフ）
ばかもん！魔界にも患者はわんさかいるんだぞ。
Fool!
I have flocks of patients back
in the Demon World, you know!
ブ～！
（ヒルダ）
呼んでみればよいではないか。
Why don't you simply call for him?
おそらく　近しい者が呼べば
とんでくると思うぞ　古市。
Perhaps he will come if someone
near-and-dear calls for him, Furuichi.
そんな…近しいって…。
呼びなさい！
I wouldn't say I'm near-and...
Do it! Or are you gonna spout
that lame pun at Miss Hilda?
それとも　あの寒いギャグを
ヒルダ姉様に言おうか？
寒いギャグ？
はい　実は…。
Lame pun?
Right! You see...
わかった！呼ぶから！
ヒルダさんに言うのはやめろ！
Wait, I'll call for him!
Just don't say it to Hilda-san!
呼んでくれるのか。
You'll call him for us?
そりゃあ　ヒルダさんの
頼みとあらば…。
Well, if it's something you request...
うむ　それはそれとして…
「ほんまかい」はないと思うぞ。
That will do, however...
HonMAKAI
That pun wasn't funny.
だっ！いやあぁ～どエス！ううぅ…！
Now you're just rubbing it in!
早く呼べよ。
ダ～ヴ～。
Hurry up and call him.
お前らは　だまってろ～！
All of you just shut up!
《近しい者が呼べば来るって…
今までの流れからして→
Calling someone near-and-dear...
At this point, I've got a sure-fire
way of getting him here.
絶対　来ちまうだろ。フフ…》
呼ばない。
I won't call for him.
（アランドロン）お呼びですかな？
You called?
さすがだな…。
ダーブ！
大したものだ。
Impressive.
I'll give you credit for that.
呼んでね～よ～！
I didn't call for you!
（アランドロン）１・２・３・４・５・６・７…。
（古市）あの…これ。
1, 2, 3, 4...
Um... Is there some reason
we're going elsewhere?
場所を変える意味は
あるんですか？
うむ　魔界への転送は特別でな…。
Yes. Transferring to the
Demon World is special.
次元をまたがねばならんぶん
水辺や山など→
We have to cross dimensions.
It requires the natural energy
of rivers or mountains.
自然のエネルギーが
必要となるのだ…。→
さらに言えば　一度に転送できる
質量も限られてくる。
Plus, there is a limit to the amount of
mass that can be transferred at once.
おそらくアランドロンといえども
無事に転送できるのは→
I believe that Alaindelon can safely
transfer no more than 2 people.
２人が限度だろうな。
ふ～ん…。
ちょっとぉ。
ああ～？まだ何か用か～？
Just a sec!
You still want something?
（ラミア）
あんたじゃないわよ。ベルゼ様に→
Not you! I wanted to say
farewell to Beelze-sama!
お別れのあいさつよ！
あ　そ…。
Oh, right.
ほい。
アブダ。
Here.
できればよ　このまま
持って帰ってもらいて～んだがな。
I wish you could just take him home instead.
あたしだって　そ～したいわよ。
I'd like to do that too!
でも　ベルゼ様が
１５メートル以上離れたら→
But if Beelze-sama gets more that 15 meters
from you, you'd be lethally electrocuted...
即死レベルの電撃を放って→
あんたが死んじゃうっていう
設定になってるし…。
That means you'd die!
アッ　アイアイ…。
ベルゼ様！
Beelze-sama... Make sure to
become a wonderful Demon Lord!
絶対　立派な魔王になって下さい！
何があっても　あたしは…
ベルゼ様の味方ですから！！
And remember... No matter what,
I'm on your side, Beelze-sama!
お～。
うむ　頼りにしているぞ。
We'll be counting on you.
また会おう　ラミア。
Until we meet again, Lamia.
ヒルダ姉様ぁ…ヒッ…→
Miss Hilda!
ヒルダ姉様～！
（ラフマニノフ）ム～。
Miss Hilda!
そろそろ行きますぞ～。
It's about time we left!
では…。
Then...
ペローン。
さようなら～！
Farewell!
（古市）
魔界か…どんな所だろうな？
The Demon World, huh?
I wonder what it's like?
けっ　興味ね～な。
どうせ陰気な所に決まってる。お？
Like I care.
I'm sure it's gloomy and depressing anyway.
うん？ベ　ベルゼ様！？
ダーブ！
B-Beelze-sama?
どうしよう…うん？この感触…。
What'll I do?
This feels like...
あ～！？い～っ！
ダーブ　ダーブ！
（ラミア）あ　足も…ひぃ～！
My arm, it's...
ま　まずい！
ベ　ベルゼ様！？
T-This is bad!
Beelze-sama!
ダブー。ブ－ッ！
（ラミア）どうして～！？
Why?
こ　これは…
ベル坊が魔界に行くってことは…。
T-This is...
Baby Beel -> Demon World
Me -> Dead
If Baby Beel heads to the
Demon World... I'm dead!
オレ　死ぬじゃん！うあ～！！
どこ行こうとしてんだ　こらぁ～！！
Where the hell do you think you're going?!
いっ！いぃ～っ！！
は　離れねぇ！
H-He won't let go!
ちょっ　引っ張らないでよ！
うるせえ！おい　一回外に出ろ！
Stop pulling on me!
Shut up! Come back out here again!
（ラミア）無茶言わないでよ！
もう転送は始まってんのよ！
Don't be crazy! The transfer
has already started!
古市！て　手伝え～！
お　おう…。
F-Furuichi, help me!
S-Sure!
そんなに引っ張んないでよ！
スケベ！
やかましい！
Don't pull on me like that, you perv!
Shut the hell up! I'm gonna die here!
死んじまうだろうが～！
ちょっ…ヒルダさんも～！
Hilda-san, you too!
（一同）ぎゃあああ～！！
はい　自分を抱き締め…
回ってからのぉ　転送！
Now, hug myself... And
do a spinning transfer!
これは…
大変な事になったのでは…。
This will be trouble.
（怪鳥）ギャア　ギャア！
あ～？
くそ　ど～なったんだ？
Crap... What happened?
（ラミア）≪目が覚めた？≫
You awake?
（魔生物）グェグルル～！
（怪鳥）ギャア　ギャア　ギャア。
おい　まさかここは…？
Hey... Don't tell me, this is...
そう…魔界よ。
Yes. It's the Demon World!
うああ～！！
（男鹿・古市）ほ　ほんまかい…？
A-Are you kidding me?!
（大魔王）ついに来たか…。
Are they finally here?
（側近）では　行くのですね？
（大魔王）フッ　聞くな…。
Then, we shall go, yes?
Enough questions!
（大魔王）リーチ。→
Reach.
どお！？カッコイイ？
ワシ　カッコイイ！？
Cool! Wasn't I just like, totally cool?!
あ？何か来たぞ。
ああ。
ウィ－！
Something's here...
（ヨップル星人）ヨパレリメー。ヌッ！！
Yopalelime...
ヨップル！
Yople!
殴っていいかな？
まてまて。
It's okay if I punch it, right?
Wait. I think it's trying to speak to us.
話しかけられてるっぽいだろ…。
ヨップル返しした方が
いいんじゃね？
マジで？
We should just say "Yople" back to it, yeah?
Seriously? Is "Yople" some kind of greeting?
ヨップルって　あいさつなのか？
う～ん…。
（古市・男鹿）ヨップル…。
Yople.
ヨ…ヨップル～！！
Yople!!
（古市・男鹿）うわ～っ！！
ヨポロメリ…パピーッ！！
Yopolomeli... papi!
ヨップルっ！
Yople!
ゴップル～！
何やってんのよ　アンタ達～。
What the hell have you people done?
いや　襲ってきたから…。
あいさつしようとしただけよ！
It attacked us.
It was just saying hi!
ヨップル星人は　この辺りじゃ
一番　友好的な悪魔部族なのよ！
The Yople aliens are the friendliest
tribe of Demons in this area!
知らね～よ　んなもん。
How the hell should I know that?
だいたい　ヨップル星人って
宇宙人か？悪魔か？
And wait... Yople Aliens?
Are they aliens or Demons?
悪夢だわ…人間を魔界に
連れて来てしまうなんて…。
Demons...
I went and brought humans
to the Demon World...
しかも…しかも　よりによって
ここは→
Plus... Plus, of all the places...
ヴラドの魔境！
（怪鳥）ギャア　ギャア　ギャア！
This is Vlad's Haunt!
ヴラドの魔境？
何だ？それは。
Vlad's Haunt?
What's that?
ヴラドの魔境！！
Vlad's Haunt!
（ラミア）かつて　時の権力者
ヴラドドラクルが探索し→
It's the valley where it's said that
the Ruler of Time, Vlad Dracul,
ガクブルで帰ってきたことから
そう呼ばれる谷！→
Shivembling = Shivering and trembling
once went exploring, and
came back all shivembling!
ブラドは言った…
「あそこ　めっちゃこわい！」→
Vlad said this:
That place is way scary!
そう　本当に　とっても恐ろしい
超危険地帯なのです。→
Yes! This is a truly
frightful, dangerous place!
太古の魔獣や
それを狙う密猟者などが→
There are ancient Demon Beasts
and poachers that are after them!
いっぱい　いるのです！
まぁ　いいんじゃね？別に。
Well, I don't really care.
なあ…アランドロンで
帰りゃいいわけだし。
Yeah. We just have to go back in Alaindelon.
そうか！アランドロン！
（アランドロン）はい…。
That's right! Alaindelon!
Yes?
（３人）あ…！
いや　かたじけない…。
I do apologize...
店員をオーバーしてしまった為か
このありさまで…。
This is what happens when you
exceed the maximum occupancy...
（男鹿・古市・ラミア）ズタボロだ…。
ブ…。
He's all banged up...
（怪鳥）ギャア　ギャア。
（アランドロン）
ゴホ　ゲホッ！あ　落ちますよ。
I'm going to fall now.
It looks like the transference
pathways are misaligned.
（アランドロン）
どうやら　転送の軌道が
ずれてしまったようですな…。→
What? There is no need to fear.
なあに　心配めされるな。
こんな傷　少し眠れば…→
A little sleep, and these
light wounds will...
あ～ほら　気持よくなってきた…。
See, I'm feeling more at ease already...
Don't go to sleep! What'll we do if you die?
（古市）寝るな！お前が死んだら
オレたちは　どうすんだ！
Yeah, seriously! Don't you die!
If you die I'll friggin' kill you!
そうだぞ　マジで！死ぬな！
死んだら　ぶっ殺す！！
フッ…なぁに
こんな所で死ねませんよ。
What? I'm not going to die
from something like this.
It's almost my daughter's
birthday, you see...
もうすぐ娘の誕生日でね…。
ドレスを買ってあげるって
約束しちまった…。
I promised to buy her a new dress...
That's a total death flag!
（古市）あきらかに
死亡フラグじゃねぇかぁ！！
ラミア！てめえ医者だろ！
何とかしろ！
Lamia, you're a doctor, aren't you?
Do something!
I have been!
さっきから　やってるわよ！
でも　師匠がいないと　こんな傷…。
But for wounds like this,
without the doctor...
あ…そういや
あのテキトーな奴は　どこ行った！？
Speaking of which...
Where'd that flaky guy go?
He was the only one who transferred properly.
彼だけは　無事転送できました。
おいい～！！
Lamia-dono... I leave the rest to you...
ラミアどの　あとの事は
たの…み…ました…ぞ。
（アランドロン）アハハハ　アハハハ
アハハハハ…。
Alaindelon!
（男鹿・古市・ラミア）アランドローン！
Okay, now you're really screwing with me!
おい　てめえ　マジふざけんなよ！
Open your eyes, you!
目ぇ開けろ　コラ！死んでる
場合じゃねぇっつってんだろ～！！
I told you, this ain't no time to die!
おい　コラ！このやろう！
容赦ね～な…。
No mercy...
I said open your damn eyes!
目ぇ開けろっつってんだよ～！
（ピピピピ…）
It's a communicator!
あっ　通信器だ！
（ピピピ…）
通信器？
A communicator?
もしもし。もしも…。
[TEL]（通信器）
その声は　ラミア？無事か？
Hello? Hello...
Is that you, Lamia?
Are you safe?
Miss Hilda!
ヒルダ姉様！
Hilda-san!
ヒルダさん！
てめ～　ヒルダ！
アダ！
Damn it, Hilda!
フォルカス先生から連絡があってな
全員　無事のようだな。
I was contacted by Doctor Furcas.
It looks like you are all safe?
But Alaindelon is...
[TEL]（ラミア）でも　アランドロンが…。
やはり定員オーバーか。
Exceeded his capacity, yes?
で　今　どこだ？
So where are you now?
[TEL]そうか。そこは　王国も
手を出せぬ非干渉地域だ。→
I see. Those lands are protected. The
Kingdom cannot lay a hand on them.
Don't tell me... Have you done
something to a local inhabitant?
まさか原住民に
手を出しておらんな？
（ラミア）それが　ヨップル星人に…。
[TEL]出したのか！？そいつは
ヴラドの番人だぞ！
Actually, there was this Yople Alien, and...
You did what?!
Yople...
Those are Vlad's watchmen!
（鼻笛）
That sound...
[TEL]その音は！？くっ　逃げろ！
仲間を呼びよせたんだ！
Run! It's calling an ally!
Its ally?
（ラミア）な　仲間って！？
Akubaba!
[TEL]アクババだ！
Akubaba?
アクババ？
ヒルダさんが乗ってきたやつ？
Like the one you rode on, Hilda-san?
In that case, you could...
あれならお前…。
おうよ！蹴り一発だ！
Yeah! One swift kick and...
Really?
そうなの？
Fools!
[TEL]バカモの！言っておくが…。
うわっ！
I should tell you...
（アクババ）グアァ～！
Wild Akubabas...
[TEL]野生のアクババは…。
（男鹿・古市）エエ！？
[TEL]でかいぞ！
むりぃ～！
...are huge!
No way!
Stop screwing with me! This thing's
a completely different creature!
てめぇ　ふざけんなよ！
完全に別の生物じゃね～か！
That's why I told you to run!
[TEL]だから逃げろと言っておるのだ。
今　お前たちは→
Right now you are considered an
enemy everywhere within Vlad!
ヴラド全域から敵として
認識されたのだ！
なら　どこに逃げたって…。
グォ～！
Then where should we be running?
ダブ…。
ダッ！
ダダダダダ…ダッ！
ウィ～。
ベル坊が立った！？
エエッ！？
アアッ！
Baby Beel is standing!
ギヨヨヨ…！
ダーブゥー！！
ベル坊！
Baby Beel!
ダーッ！
ギョエ～！グア～ッ！
ヒュ～。
グオオ…！
ワダ！
Whoa! Did he power up from
coming to the Demon World?
すげぇ　魔界に来て
パワーアップしてんのか？
[TEL]フン　本来の坊っちゃまの力に
助けられたようだな。→
It sounds like you were saved
by the master's true power.
But you shouldn't let down your
guard. Listen exactly to what I say.
だが油断するな！
私の言うことをしっかり聞け。→
You are to search out Alaindelon's
daughter. Ask her to transfer you.
アランドロンの娘を捜してもらう
その娘に転送を頼むのだ！→
Do not fear, I will guide you.
案ずるな！私が案内しよう。
あっそ。
Oh, got it.
Humans, huh? That's a rare
prey. What'll we do, Gallé?
（エッダ）人間か…珍しい獲物だな。
どうする？ガレ。
（ガレ）フッ…。
Man... Why do I have to
be in a place this nuts?
…ったく　なんでこんな→
わけわかんねぇとこ
歩かなきゃなんねえんだよ！
Stop your grumbling! We're just
doing exactly as Miss Hilda says.
（ラミア）ぶつぶつうるさいわよ！→
ヒルダ姉様の指示通りなんだから。
ちっ！
I'm thirsty!
あ～　のどかわいた～！
腹へった～！
And I'm hungry!
ふぁぁ～…あっ！
リンゴらあ！んぐんぐ…。
An apple!
んぐっ！？
グハッ！にっげぇ～！
何だこりゃあ！
So bitter! What the heck?
（魔界リンゴ）食べましたね？
You ate it, didn't you?
ウウ…？
Where? Where have you gone, Yukie?!
[TV]（伸治）どこだ！どこに
行ったんだ　ゆきえ～！
Shinji-san, if you truly love
me, you'll know that I'm here!
[TV]（ゆきえ）《伸治さん　私を本当に
愛しているなら→
ここにいる事がわかるはず》
[TV]こっちに　ゆきえの気配が！
I can sense Yukie over there!
No! I'm over here, Shinji-san!
[TV]《違う！私はこっちよ
伸治さん！》
[TV]いるんだろう　ゆきえ！
この　雪の中に！
Are you here, Yukie? Somewhere in this snow!
[TV]《ゆきえはここ…伸治さん
早く会いたい…なのに…》
Yukie is right here, Shinji-san...
I want to see you, and yet...
[TV]ハハハ　そこか　ゆきえ！
そう！そこだ！
There you are Yukie! Yes, there!
Yukie!
[TV]ゆきえ～！
[TV]♪♪～
And the two pass by each other once again.
[TV]またしても
すれ違う二人であった。
It's no use. Let's end this, Shinji-san!
[TV]（ゆきえ）だめ　もう終わりよ
伸治さん。
Yukie!
[TV]（伸治）ゆきえ～！
（ゆきえ）伸治さん！
Shinji-san!
Yukie!
（ピピピピ…）
Shinji-san!
Yukie!
What is it?
どうした？
[TEL]（古市）ぎゃああ～！
うがが…うがうが…。
Please, eat more!
（魔界リンゴ）
もっと召し上がって下さい。
It looks like it's forcing him to eat.
（ラミア）
何か食べさせられてますね。
A Demon Apple Tree, yes?
[TEL]魔界リンゴだな
あの手この手で　自らの実を→
They force you to eat their
fruit through any means.
食べさせようとする。
なに　そのうち飽きる。
Don't worry, it'll get bored soon enough.
Soon enough?
そ　そのうちって…。
うがあ！うぐぐ…。
にゃははは…！ああ？
あ？
さあ　あなたも。
Now, you too!
いらねえよ。
Don't want any.
ウ…ああ…。
ひどい…あたしだって　苦いって
事ぐらい分かってるんです。
How cruel... I know that I'm bitter...
And I know that my skins
are dry, and I'm tall...
おまけに肌カサカサだし
身長高いし…→
But I almost never get any customers
in a dark, damp place like this!
でも　こんな暗くて
ジメジメしたとこ　お客さん→
なかなか来てくれないんですぅ～。
助けると思って→
It'll really help me if you just eat one...
どうか１つだけでも…。
I said I don't want any.
だから　いらねえって！
（魔界リンゴ）オオオ…。
普通…ここまで言えば
食べるでしょうがぁ～！
A normal person would just
eat it after saying all this!
Apple!
アップルゥ！
アアア～！
お前…。
どっちが悪魔か→
You...
I can't tell which one's the Demon here...
わかりゃしないわね。
ダ～ブ！
[TV]（伸治）たとえ悪魔と言われよ
うと　君を愛し続ける！
Even if you call me a demon,
I'll keep on loving you!
You're a demon! A demon, I say!
おおお…。
（ピピピ…）
今度は何だ？
落ち着けんではないか。
What is it now?
Haven't things calmed down?
The flower...!
（古市）ぎゃああ～！
何でオレばっか！→
Why is it always me? Stop it, that tickles!
や　やめろ！くすぐったい！
アハハハ！→
What is it this time?
お？今度は何…ウグッ！→
くさ～い！すごいくさい！
ああ　すげぇ！アア～！
Man, this stinks!
A Demon Rafflesia, I suppose?
[TEL]魔界ラフレシアだな。→
It catches its prey through a special scent.
匂いを相手に付着させようとする。なに　そのうち飽きる。
Don't worry. It'll get bored soon enough.
What the hell does soon enough mean?!
だから　そのうちって…
ぶはっ！くっせ～！
Eww!
（古市）うわ～！アア～！
Yople!
ヨップル！
The hell... Man.
何だ　あれ…ったく。
You really saved me there!
いやぁ　助かったよ。
（ラミア・男鹿）ウッ！…くっさ～！
You stink!
W-Wait! Wait for me!
待て！待てよ～！
（怪鳥）ギョエエ～！
あれか？
Is that it?
ああ　誰かさんのお陰で
思いのほか　早く着けたようだな。
Thanks to the help of someone, we
arrived faster than we thought.
何で離れて立ってるんだ？
俺たちは道を行くから　おめ～は
そっちの川を泳いで行け。
Why are you standing so far from me?
We'll go on the road. You swim up the river.
Agreed.
（ラミア）賛成～。
（古市）く　くっそ～！
Damn you!
これが　アランドロンの家か。
（ラミア）違う違う　娘さんの家。→
So this is Alaindelon's house?
No, no... This is his daughter's house.
She seems to do research
on ancient Demon Beasts.
何でも古代の魔獣研究家らしいわ。
That's why she lives so far out
from the Demon Kingdom, I hear.
それで　こんな魔境の外れに
住んでるんだって。
（古市）ウウ～　水が冷たかった！
か　風邪ひいちまう…。
The water was freezing!
I'm gonna catch a cold...
おっ　ホントに泳いできたのか？
テメェ！
You actually swam up here?
You bastard!
ってか…ハ～　どうにも
テンション上がらねえなぁ。
And hey...
I just can't get excited about this.
About what?
何がだ？
ダ？
I mean, think about it, man.
だってお前　想像してみろよ。
あのおっさんの娘だぜ。
She's his daughter!
I bet she's all...
きっと　こんな感じの…。
((アハ～ン　チュッ))
フッ　イメージが貧困だな
もっと　こんな感じだろ…。
You've got such a pitiful imagination.
She'd be more like this, right?
((シャア！))
ダダダン！
あ？違うって？
What? You say that's not it?
Then, how about you, Baby Beel?
じゃあ　ベル坊は　どんな？
ダ～ブ～！
((ダ～ブ～))
（古市・男鹿）おお～！
Are you all idiots?
バッカじゃないの？っていうか
全員ヒゲはえてるんですけど→
And they all had mustaches...
Even Beelze-sama's squid...
ベルゼ様のはイカだし。
（ラミア）ごめんくださ～い。→
Excuse us!
The door is open, so we'll be coming inside.
扉　開いてるので
入りま～す…なっ！
（男鹿・古市）アッ！？
（古市）廃墟？
Abandoned?
いいえ　違うわ。
荒れ方が　まだ新しい。
No...
The broken stuff is still new.
[TEL]誰もいねえぞ。
There isn't anyone here.
Perhaps it was the poachers.
密猟者かもしれんな。
[TEL]（古市）密猟者？
Poachers?
Yes.
ああ。魔境の珍しい魔獣などを
売りさばいている連中だ。
They're people who sell rare Demon Beasts...
[TEL]娘の転送能力を
狙ったのかもしれん。
They may have been after
her ability to transfer.
Yes, that's right!
（ガレ）そう　その通り！
で　お前らも
商品になるってわけだ。→
And you people are going to become my wares!
Weak humans can't stand up to us!
非力な人間が抵抗するんじゃ
ないぞ。エッダ　任せる！
Edda, handle this!
Yeah!
おう！フッ！
うおお～！
（ドカッ！ドカッ！）
え？…わぁっ！
わあ～っ！
ダ～！
ヨップル。
Yople.
Wait, wha...?
あれ？ちょっ…まて　まて！
お前　本当に人間か？
W-Wait, hold it... Are you really a human?
あ！その紋章は…！
That mark...
王家の紋！王族の契約者だと～！？
That's the Royal Crest!
You're in a contract with the royal family?
That's right Yople!
そうですよっプル！
（ガレ）ゴップル！
Yople!
[TEL]そいつらの根城が
近くにあるはずだ。→
Their base should be nearby.
I bet she is there.
おそらく娘もそこだろう。
In other words, we have to go rescue her!
（ラミア）
ということは　助けに行かなきゃ
いけないわけですね。
はぁ…ややこしい事になったな。
あっ？写真？
This has started to get complicated...
A picture?
Hey, Furuichi...
おい　古市　今度は
盗賊退治だとよ。面倒くせえなぁ。
We're going to wipe out
a band of thieves now.
Man, what a pain.
What are you saying, Oga-kun?
何を言っているんだ　男鹿君。
あ？
か弱い女性が助けを
求めているんだ！行くぞ！
Our goal is to rescue the lovely damsel!
Let us go!
は？
ウィ。
ハッ！
As things are, they would have had
no choice but to head there...
こうなれば
あそこに向かうしかありませんな。
あそこに行けば　何かが
わかるのでございますよ！
If I go there, I'll learn something!
ツヅクップル。
To be Yopled.
Our trip has only yet begun!
As have my adventures!
Yople!
Yopelalime?
Wait, my darling!
Yople!
Yopolomelopapi!
And cut it out with the Yoples already!
And who the hell is this "lovely"?
It's Alaindelon's daughter, duh!
Wait for me. I will save you, for sure!
And Furuichi put on a very happy face.
On the next Beelzebub:
Welcome Back, Demon World!
When this battle is over,
I'm going to get marri...
Yople!
Gople!